Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- DEPARTMENT OF STATE FILE, 1973-1974 (Boxes 150-164)
  - Speeches and engagements
    - Overseas Development Council International Development Conference, Washington, D.C., 1973 October 25 (Box-folder 156: 1)
      Includes speech and drafts.
    - Chamber of Commerce International Committee dinner, Washington, D.C., 1973 October 29 (Box-folder 156: 2)
    - Italian television interview, Washington, D.C., 1973 November 12 (Box-folder 156: 3)
    - National Foreign Trade Council convention, New York City, 1973 November 13 (Box-folder 156: 4)
    - White House meeting with business leaders, Washington, D.C., 1973 November 14 (Box-folder 156: 5)
    - Department of State Foreign Service Day program, Washington, D.C., 1973 November 16 (Box-folder 156: 6)
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee hearings on replenishment of International Development Association and Development Bank special funds, Washington, D.C., 1973 November 19 (Box-folder 156: 7)
    - Securities Industry Association annual convention, Boca Raton, Florida, 1973 November 29 (Box-folder 156: 8)
    - Suffolk County Boy Scouts Council dinner, Hauppauge, New York, 1973 December 4 (Box-folder 156: 9)
    - House Government Operations Committee hearings on establishment of a Federal Energy Administration, Washington, D.C., 1973 December 10 (Box-folder 156: 10)
    - U.S.-USSR Trade and Economic Council meeting, Washington, D.C., 1973 December 12 (Box-folder 156: 11)
    - Washington Industrial Round Table luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1974 January 9 (Box-folder 157: 1)
    - Senate Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs Committee Subcommittee on International Finance hearings on foreign investment in the United States, Washington, D.C., 1974 January 23 (Box-folder 157: 2)
      Includes testimony and notes
    - Department of State Seminar on Technology Exchange with the USSR, Washington, D.C., 1974 February 28 (Box-folder 157: 3)
    - Public Affairs Council luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1974 February 28 (Box-folder 157: 4)
    - Lecture on world economy, Adelphi University, Garden City, New York, 1974 March 3
      - Speech (Box-folder 157: 5)
      - Correspondence and background materials (Box-folder 158: 1)
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee hearings on Department of State budget, Washington, D.C., 1974 March 11 (Box-folder 158: 2)
    - Engagements declined
      - General (Box-folder 158: 3-4)
      - Bilderberg Meetings (Box-folder 158: 5)
  - Annual foreign policy report for 1973 (Box-folder 158: 6)
  - Correspondence
    - A-B (Box-folder 158: 7)
    - Barreaux, Theodore C. (Box-folder 158: 8)
    - C (Box-folder 158: 9)
    - Cherne, Leo (Box-folder 158: 10)
    - D (Box-folder 159: 1)
    - DeLisser, Horace E. (Box-folder 159: 2)
    - E (Box-folder 159: 3)
    - Engelstad, Sam (Box-folder 159: 4)
    - F (Box-folder 159: 5)
    - Friedman, Samuel J. (Box-folder 159: 6)
    - G (Box-folder 159: 7)
    - Guttman, Egon (Box-folder 159: 8)
    - H (Box-folder 159: 9)
    - Haldeman, H. R. (Box-folder 159: 10)
    - Helms, Richard (Box-folder 159: 11)
    - Howley, John (Box-folder 159: 12)
    - Hrubý, Blahoslav (Box-folder 159: 13)
    - J-L (Box-folder 159: 14)
    - Lange, Keith (Box-folder 159: 15)
    - Lent, Norman F. (Box-folder 159: 16)
    - M (Box-folder 159: 17)
    - McTague, Peter J. (Box-folder 159: 18)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 159: 19)
    - N-S (Box-folder 159: 20)
  - Publicity. Press coverage of WJC
    - General (Box-folder 159: 21)
    - Finance (Box-folder 159: 22)
  - House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee and its Special Subcommittee on Investigations continuing investigation into International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation and Robert Vesco affairs, 1973 May-November
    - Documents file of chronology and significant items, as arranged by WJC (Box-folder 160: 1)
    - Testimony by G. Bradford Cook, 1973 May 14 (Box-folder 160: 2)
    - Statement by WJC, 1973 May 29 (Box-folder 160: 3)
    - Letter by WJC to New York Times re its coverage, 1973 June 2 (Box-folder 160: 4)
    - Testimony of Ralph E. Erickson before subcommittee, 1973 June 6 (Box-folder 160: 5)
    - Testimony of WJC before subcommittee, 1973 June 26 (Box-folder 160: 6-7)
    - Testimony of WJC before subcommittee, 1973 June 28 (Box-folder 160: 8)
    - Statements to committee re staffing of Securities and Exchange Commission, 1973 July (Box-folder 161: 1)
    - Statement by WJC to committee, 1973 November 2 (Box-folder 161: 2)
    - Extracts from testimony (Box-folder 161: 3)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 161: 4)
    - Miscellaneous statements and memoranda (Box-folder 161: 5)
    - Drafts of statements and testimony (Box-folder 161: 6)
    - Notes (Box-folder 162: 1)
    - Department of State telegrams (mainly transcriptions of press coverage) (Box-folder 162: 2)
    - Press coverage (Box-folder 162: 3)
    - Background materials (Box-folder 162: 4-5)
  - Subject file
    Correspondence, memoranda, studies, reports, and printed matter
    - Ayco Corporation (Box-folder 163: 1)
    - Capital markets (Box-folder 163: 2)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box-folder 163: 3)
    - Developing countries (Box-folder 163: 4-5)
    - Energy (Box-folder 163: 6)
    - Foreign Portfolio Sales Corporation proposal (Box-folder 163: 7)
    - International capital markets
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 163: 8)
      - Memoranda, studies and background materials (Box-folder 164: 1-2)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 164: 3)
    - Securities, Commodities and Capital Markets Committee (interdepartmental) (Box-folder 164: 4)
    - Technology transfer. (Box-folder 164: 5)
      Draft memorandum by WJC, "Limiting Trade in Technology on Economic Grounds"
    - Tripartite Businessmen's Conference (Puerto Rico, 1974) (Box-folder 164: 6)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 164: 7)
- COMMISSION ON THE ORGANIZATION OF THE GOVERNMENT FOR THE CONDUCT OF FOREIGN POLICY FILE, 1973-1975 (Boxes 165-168)
  Papers of Casey as a member of the Commission on the Organization of the Government for the Conduct of Foreign Policy, a temporary commission created by act of Congress.
  - Appointment (Box-folder 165: 1)
    Correspondence, memoranda, and statutory authorization of Commission
  - Meetings
    Minutes, agenda and background meeting materials
    - 1973 April 16 (Box-folder 165: 2)
    - 1973 July 30 (Box-folder 165: 3)
    - 1973 September 17 (Box-folder 165: 4)
    - 1973 October 15-16 (Box-folder 165: 5)
    - 1973 November 19-20 (Box-folder 165: 6)
    - 1973 December 14 (Box-folder 165: 7)
    - 1974 January 21-22 (Box-folder 165: 8)
    - 1975 June 3 (Box-folder 165: 9)
  - Correspondence and memoranda (Box-folder 165: 10)
  - Reports, studies and statements received
    Includes formal statements by Commission members, reports and studies especially written for the Commission, and submissions to the Commission by government agencies
    - WJC statement to Commission on international economic policy, 1974 February 26 (Box-folder 165: 11)
    - Allison, Graham T. et al., "Defense and Arms Control Study." Seven volumes plus overview volume (Box-folder 165: 12)
    - Allison, Graham T. et al., "Defense and Arms Control Study" (contd.) (Box-folder 166: 1-3)
    - Barnds, William J., "Intelligence Functions" and "Intelligence and Policymaking in an Institutional Context" (Box-folder 166: 4)
    - Brown, T. A., "Comments on 'Innovations in Intelligence Production' by C. W. Kelly III" (Box-folder 166: 5)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, "Toward an Open Foreign Policy" (Box-folder 166: 6)
    - Central Intelligence Agency. Submissions by William E. Colby (Box-folder 166: 7)
    - Coulam, Robert F., "The Importance of the Beginning: Defense Doctrine and the Development of the F-111 Fighter-Bomber" (Box-folder 167: 1)
    - Crocker, Chester A., "The President's External Advisors in Foreign Policy" (Box-folder 167: 2)
    - Department of Defense. Submission by Robert C. Hill (Box-folder 167: 3)
    - Department of State. Submissions by Charles W. Robinson and others (Box-folder 167: 4)
    - Griffenhagen-Kroeger, Inc.
      - "U.S. Foreign Economic Policy: Case Studies and Analysis in Decision-Making and Organization: The U.S.-Japan Textile Dispute, 1969-1971" and "The Dollar Devaluations of 1971 and 1973: A Case Study in Foreign Economic Policy Decision-Making" (Box-folder 167: 5)
      - "Cases on a Decade of United States Foreign Economic Policy, 1965-74." Two volumes (Box-folder 167: 6)
      - "Cases on a Decade of United States Foreign Economic Policy, 1965-74" (contd.) (Box-folder 168: 1)
    - Hudson Institute. "Synoptic Context One: The Prospects for Mankind and a Year 2000 Ideology" (Box-folder 168: 2)
    - Library of Congress Congressional Research Service. William C. Gibbons, "Reexamining the Conduct of Foreign Policy: A Prospectus" (Box-folder 168: 3)
    - McGlinn, Frank C. P. (Commission member). Statement (Box-folder 168: 4)
    - Pearson, James B. (Commission member). Statement (Box-folder 168: 5)
    - Prince Analysis, Inc. "Toward the Improvement of Foreign Service Field Reporting" (Box-folder 168: 6)
    - Reckford, Thomas J., "Conference on the CIA and Covert Action" (Box-folder 168: 7)
    - United States Information Agency. Submissions by Edward Hidalgo and James Keogh (Box-folder 168: 8)
    - Wagner, Stanley P. (Commission member). Statement
      - Report (Box-folder 168: 9)
      - Drafts (Box-folder 168: 10)
        Includes contributions by WJC
      - Final version (untitled), 1975 June 27 (Box-folder 168: 11)
  - Publicity. Press coverage (Box-folder 168: 12)
- EXPORT-IMPORT BANK FILE, 1974-1976 (Boxes 169-187)
  Papers of Casey as president and chairman of the Export-Import Bank of the United States.
  - Appointment (Box-folder 169: 1)
    Press releases and announcements
  - Congratulatory letters upon appointment (Box-folder 169: 2)
  - Confirmation hearings
    The confirmation process, extending from 1973 December to 1974 March, afforded an occasion for renewed examination of the International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation and Robert Vesco affairs
    - Documents file of significant letters and testimony, as arranged by WJC (Box-folder 169: 3)
    - Testimony of WJC before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Washington, D.C., 1973 December 12 (Box-folder 169: 4)
    - Statement by WJC, 1974 February 4. (Box-folder 169: 5)
      Includes drafts
    - Correspondence
      - Boltz, Gerald E. (Box-folder 169: 6)
      - Cohen, Manuel F. (Box-folder 169: 7)
      - Erickson, Ralph E. (Box-folder 169: 8)
      - House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box-folder 169: 9)
      - Legal advisers to WJC
        - Gould, Milton (Box-folder 170: 1)
        - Others (Box-folder 170: 2)
      - Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs (Box-folder 170: 3)
      - United States Attorney's Office (John R. Wing) (Box-folder 170: 4)
      - Watergate Special Prosecution Force (Leon Jaworski) (Box-folder 170: 5)
      - White House officials (Box-folder 170: 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 170: 7)
    - Financial disclosure statements (Box-folder 170: 8)
    - Extracts from hearings (Box-folder 170: 9)
      Includes extracts from confirmation hearings of WJC as under secretary of state
    - Notes and drafts (Box-folder 170: 10)
    - Publicity
      Press coverage and correspondence of WJC re press coverage
      - General (Box-folder 170: 11)
      - Business Week (Box-folder 170: 12)
    - Follow-up report. Sanitized version of report by Watergate Special Prosecution Force ITT Task Force (Box-folder 171: 1)
      1975 August
  - Appointment schedules
    - 1974 March-April (Box-folder 171: 2)
    - 1974 May-July (Box-folder 171: 3)
  - Speeches and engagements
    Correspondence, memoranda, agenda, meeting and background materials, and press coverage. Speech transcripts are noted when present
    - Multinational Corporations Symposium, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1974 March 16 (Box-folder 171: 4)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency symposium, Reston, Virginia, 1974 March 29-31 (Box-folder 171: 5)
    - Radio broadcast taping with Congressman Robert J. Huber, Washington, D.C., 1974 April 25 (Box-folder 171: 6)
    - House Committee on Banking and Currency Subcommittee on International Trade hearings on extension of the charter of the Export-Import Bank, Washington, D.C., 1974 April 30 (Box-folder 171: 7)
    - President's "E" Award for Export Service presentation to the Marine Office--Appleton and Cox Corporation, New York City, 1974 May 2 (Box-folder 171: 8)
    - Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry meeting, Hempstead, New York, 1974 May 3 (Box-folder 171: 9)
    - National Venture Capital Association annual meeting, New York City, 1974 May 15 (Box-folder 172: 1)
    - Aerospace Industries Association Williamsburg Conference, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1974 May 23 (Box-folder 172: 2)
    - International Management and Development Institute meeting, Washington, D.C., 1974 June 3 (Box-folder 172: 3)
    - Conference Board meeting, New York City, 1974 June 6 (Box-folder 172: 4)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company dinner in honor of WJC, Washington, D.C., 1974 June 27 (Box-folder 172: 5)
    - Press conference re new Export-Import Bank policies, Washington, D.C., 1974 July 9 (Box-folder 172: 6)
      Includes transcript
    - Television and radio interview, 1974 July 11 (Box-folder 172: 7)
    - Japan-America Society annual meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1974 July 23 (Box-folder 172: 8)
    - Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs hearings on energy production, Washington, D.C., 1974 July 25 (Box-folder 172: 9)
    - U.S.-Soviet Trade Mission meeting, New York City, 1974 August 13 (Box-folder 172: 10)
    - Agency for International Development-American University Overseas Mission radio and television broadcast taping, Washington, D.C., 1974 August 16 (Box-folder 173: 1)
      Includes transcript.
    - Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry World Trade Club meeting, Jericho, New York, 1974 September 23 (Box-folder 173: 2)
    - Containerization Institute meeting, Washington, D.C., 1974 October 9 (Box-folder 173: 3)
    - Finance Magazine Banker of the Year Award dinner in honor of Arthur Burns, New York City, 1974 October 14 (Box-folder 173: 4)
    - Chamber of Commerce International Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., 1974 October 17 (Box-folder 173: 5)
    - Export-Import Bank Minerals Conference, Washington, D.C., 1974 October 18 (Box-folder 173: 6)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission 40th anniversary dinner, Washington, D.C., 1974 October 24 (Box-folder 173: 7)
    - World Affairs Council of Boston and International Center of New England meeting, Boston, Massachusetts, 1974 November 20 (Box-folder 173: 8)
    - Export-Import Bank Engineering and Construction Conference, Washington, D.C., 1974 November 22 (Box-folder 173: 9)
    - Mid-America Committee luncheon, Chicago, Illinois, 1974 November 26 (Box-folder 174: 1)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. annual dinner with William J. Donovan Award presentation to WJC, Washington, D.C., 1974 December 5 (Box-folder 174: 2)
    - New York University annual Dean's Day homecoming, New York City, 1974 December 7 (Box-folder 174: 3)
    - Machinery and Allied Products Institute seminar on U.S. exports, Arlington, Virginia, 1974 December 13 (Box-folder 174: 4)
    - Arthur D. Little, Inc., Corporate Directors Conference, Washington, D.C., 1974 December 16 (Box-folder 174: 5)
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies session, Salzburg, Austria, 1975 January 4 (Box-folder 174: 6)
    - American Chamber of Commerce in Austria luncheon, Vienna, 1975 January 9 (Box-folder 175: 1)
    - Louise Academy lecture, Chung-ang University, Seoul, South Korea, 1975 January 30 (Box-folder 175: 2)
    - University of Rochester Executive Development Seminar, Washington, D.C., 1975 February 21 (Box-folder 175: 3)
    - Export-Import Bank East-West Round Table, Washington, D.C., 1975 February 21 (Box-folder 175: 4)
    - Practising Law Institute session on the Securities and Exchange Commission, Washington, D.C., 1975 February 28-March 1 (Box-folder 175: 5)
    - Association of Secretaries of Chambers of Foreign Commerce in the United States luncheon, New York City, 1975 March 4 (Box-folder 175: 6)
    - Diplomatic and Consular Officers (Retired) Far East Group luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1975 March 5 (Box-folder 175: 7)
    - Newcomen Society in North America dinner in honor of the Deak-Perera Group, New York City, 1975 March 20 (Box-folder 175: 8)
    - Cleveland Council on World Affairs annual meeting, Cleveland, Ohio, 1975 March 21 (Box-folder 175: 9)
    - International Executives Association conference, New York City, 1975 March 25 (Box-folder 175: 10)
    - International Road Federation meeting, Washington, D.C., 1975 March 26 (Box-folder 175: 11)
    - Bankers' Association for Foreign Trade convention, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 1975 April 7-8 (Box-folder 175: 12)
    - American-Arab Association for Commerce and Industry meeting, New York City, 1975 April 10 (Box-folder 176: 1)
    - Atomic Industrial Forum/Danatom International Conference on Nuclear Power and the Money Market, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1975 April 17 (Box-folder 176: 2)
    - International Accounting Conference, New York City, 1975 May 5 (Box-folder 176: 3)
    - Governor's Conference on World Trade, Tampa, Florida, 1975 May 21-22 (Box-folder 176: 4)
    - Romanian-U.S. Economic Council annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1975 May 30 (Box-folder 176: 5)
    - Senate Committee on Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Operations hearings on Export-Import Bank budget request, Washington, D.C., 1975 June 11 (Box-folder 176: 6)
    - American-Hellenic Institute luncheon in honor of Xenophon Zolotas, Washington, D.C., 1975 September 5 (Box-folder 176: 7)
    - Trip to Mexico and Venezuela, 1975 September 22-27 (Box-folder 176: 8)
    - American Mining Congress convention, San Francisco, California, 1975 October 1 (Box-folder 177: 1)
    - American Bar Association Standing Committee on Education about Communism workshop, Washington, D.C., 1975 October 17 (Box-folder 177: 2)
    - Republic of China-U.S. Conference on Investment, Trade and Tourism, Houston, Texas, 1975 November 5 (Box-folder 177: 3)
    - New York District Export Council meeting, New York City, 1975 November 18 (Box-folder 177: 4)
    - Fordham University Corporate Law Institute seminar, New York City, 1975 November 18 (Box-folder 177: 5)
    - Middle East Institute bi-annual Seminar on American Business in the Middle East and North Africa, Washington, D.C., 1975 December 5 (Box-folder 177: 6)
    - Chemical Specialties Manufacturers Association annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1975 December 8 (Box-folder 177: 7)
    - Engagements declined (Box-folder 177: 8)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified speech drafts (Box-folder 177: 9)
    - Background material for speeches
      - Speeches by others (Box-folder 178: 1-3)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 179: 1)
  - Correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 179: 2)
    - B (Box-folder 179: 3)
    - Boyle, Richard L. (Box-folder 179: 4)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 179: 5)
    - C (Box-folder 179: 6)
    - Cherne, Leo (Box-folder 179: 7)
    - Cook, G. Bradford (Box-folder 179: 8)
    - Corcoran, Thomas G. (Box-folder 179: 9)
    - D (Box-folder 179: 10)
    - Deak, Nicholas L. (Box-folder 179: 11)
    - Dickler, Gerald (Box-folder 179: 12)
    - E (Box-folder 180: 1)
    - F (Box-folder 180: 2)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box-folder 180: 3)
    - Friedman, Samuel J. (Box-folder 180: 4)
    - G (Box-folder 180: 5)
    - Garrett, Ray, Jr. (Box-folder 180: 6)
    - H (Box-folder 180: 7)
    - Hall, Leonard W. (Box-folder 180: 8)
    - Hoxie, R. Gordon (Box-folder 180: 9)
    - I (Box-folder 180: 10)
    - J (Box-folder 180: 11)
    - K (Box-folder 180: 12)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 180: 13)
    - L (Box-folder 180: 14)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 180: 15)
    - Leibman, Morris I. (Box-folder 180: 16)
    - Lent, Norman F. (Box-folder 180: 17)
    - M (Box-folder 180: 18)
    - Manning, Elizabeth MacDonald (Box-folder 180: 19)
    - N (Box-folder 181: 1)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 181: 2)
    - Novick, David (Box-folder 181: 3)
    - O (Box-folder 181: 4)
    - P-Q (Box-folder 181: 5)
    - R (Box-folder 181: 6)
    - Regan, Donald T. (Box-folder 181: 7)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 181: 8)
    - Rosselli, Jean-Pierre (Box-folder 181: 9)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald (Box-folder 181: 10)
    - S (Box-folder 181: 11)
    - Scott, Harold B. (Box-folder 181: 12)
    - Sears, Harry L. (Box-folder 181: 13)
    - Stans, Maurice H. (Box-folder 181: 14)
    - T (Box-folder 181: 15)
    - U-V (Box-folder 181: 16)
    - W (Box-folder 181: 17)
    - Y-Z (Box-folder 181: 18)
  - Addresses (Box-folder 181: 19)
  - Addresses (contd.) (Box-folder 182: 1-3)
  - Reports and memoranda
    - General (Box-folder 182: 4)
    - Fiscal year report to President Gerald R. Ford by WJC, 1975 July 3 (Box-folder 182: 5)
  - Publications (of Export-Import Bank)
    - Annual Report
      - 1974 (Box-folder 183: 1)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 183: 2-3)
    - Brochures (Box-folder 183: 4)
  - Personnel recruitment file (Box-folder 183: 5)
  - Publicity (Box-folder 183: 6)
    Biographical data and press coverage re WJC
  - Subject file
    Correspondence, memoranda, reports, studies, notes, and printed matter
    - Capital markets (Box-folder 183: 7)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box-folder 183: 8)
    - Commodities (Box-folder 184: 1)
    - Elections--1974 (Malcolm Wilson New York gubernatorial campaign) (Box-folder 184: 2)
    - Energy
      - General (Box-folder 184: 3)
      - Offshore oil drilling (Box-folder 184: 4)
    - Exchange rates (Box-folder 184: 5)
    - Export invisibles (Box-folder 184: 6)
    - Food production (Box-folder 184: 7)
    - Industries (Box-folder 184: 8)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development/International Monetary Fund Boards of Governors annual meetings (Washington, D.C., 1975) (Box-folder 185: 1)
    - Loan agreement terms (Box-folder 185: 2)
    - Loan projects
      - Algeria (Box-folder 185: 3)
      - Argentina (Box-folder 185: 4)
      - Brazil (Box-folder 185: 5)
      - Egypt (Box-folder 185: 6)
      - Korea (Box-folder 185: 7)
      - Soviet Union (Box-folder 185: 8)
      - Spain (Box-folder 185: 9)
      - Taiwan (Box-folder 185: 10)
      - Yugoslavia (Box-folder 185: 11)
      - Zaire (Box-folder 185: 12)
    - Multinational corporations
      - Notes and drafts (Box-folder 185: 13)
      - Memoranda and reports (Box-folder 185: 14)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 186: 1)
    - Retained income reserve for contingencies and defaults (Box-folder 186: 2)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box-folder 186: 3)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box-folder 186: 4)
    - World Monetary Disorder Conference (Pepperdine University, 1974) (Box-folder 186: 5)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 187: 1)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 187: 2)
  - Retirement from government employment, 1976 January (Box-folder 187: 3)
    Personnel records
- CASEY MEMORIAL FUND FILE, 1987-1988 (Boxes 379-395)
  Financial records of the William J. Casey Memorial Fund for aid to Nicaraguan guerrillas, arranged numerically by deposit number. Includes letters and cards accompanying contributions.
  - 1-24 (Box-folder 379: 1)
  - 25-48 (Box-folder 379: 2)
  - 49-72 (Box-folder 379: 3)
  - 73-96 (Box-folder 379: 4)
  - 97-120 (Box-folder 379: 5)
  - 121-145 (Box-folder 379: 6)
  - 146-170 (Box-folder 380: 1)
  - 171-194 (Box-folder 380: 2)
  - 195-218 (Box-folder 380: 3)
  - 219-242 (Box-folder 380: 4)
  - 243-266 (Box-folder 380: 5)
  - 267-290 (Box-folder 381: 1)